<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Galleries on Sam O-C</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/gallery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Galleries on Sam O-C</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:17:21 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/gallery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Student Futures Manifesto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gallery/sfm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:17:21 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gallery/sfm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amnesty</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gallery/amnesty/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:16:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gallery/amnesty/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NixOS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gallery/nixos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 18:00:22 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gallery/nixos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As with LaTeX, I found out about NixOS during a Wikipedia Binge, and decided to try it as I have been vaguely involved in the Linux Desktop scene for about 11 Years.  As such, the idea of a Functional Paradigm based Package Management System was certainly interesting, and since I had recently fubar&amp;rsquo;d my Ubuntu Install (due to not understanding DKMS modules and the fact that ZFS on Ubuntu was reliant on them), I thought I&amp;rsquo;d give NixOS a try.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaTeX</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gallery/latex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:32:17 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gallery/latex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;how-i-found-a-love-for-latex&#34;&gt;How I found a love for LaTeX.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I first came across LaTeX during a Wikipedia Binge whilst in Sixth Form (Year 12 specifically) and it piqued my interest owing to my strong dislike of the clunky and slow MS Word and the fast but limited Notepad.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, I began to try to learn LaTeX, at first I struggled, after all, what 17 Year Old would want to learn something almost exclusively used in academic and technical publishing. But the results spoke for themselves, the neat, clear typesetting; the ease of just having to worry about the contents, with the compiler doing all the (not) fun bits of layouts and image placements and the like.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
